At the very moment
you start exercising
when oxygen hasn't kicked in yet
but your muscles are
already on the move
in that very brief moment
your body needs
energy it can use right away.
So, at the start of exercise
what kind of energy
metabolism takes the lead?
Yoo Chae-min.
I'll find out by next week.
What?
I think seeing your students
grow week by week
could be your joy, Professor.
Yeah.
It's the ATP and creatine
phosphate in muscles.
Alright, everyone heard
Han Se-woon, right?
Let's get serious P.E. majors.
Huh?
Han Se-woon?
[Episode 2]
[Ongoing Misunderstandings]
You really think that's tasty?
I usually like
what others don't.
Is it why I'm not
interested in guys?
Han Se-woon?